<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet href="css/questionnaire&table_style.css"?>


<FoodList>
  

  <food>
    <Name>Naan</Name>
    <Description>Traditional flatbread made with wheat flour and baked in a tandoor.</Description>
  </food>

  <food>
    <Name>Karahi</Name>
    <Description>Spicy and aromatic curry made with meat (chicken, lamb, or goat) and cooked in a karahi (wok).</Description>
  </food>

  <food>
    <Name>Korma</Name>
    <Description>Mild and creamy curry made with meat (chicken, beef, or lamb) and yogurt or cream.</Description>
  </food>

  <food>
    <Name>Haleem</Name>
    <Description>Slow-cooked stew made with meat (usually beef or chicken) and lentils.</Description>
  </food>

  <food>
    <Name>Paye</Name>
    <Description>Slow-cooked trotters or cow feet stew, often enjoyed for breakfast or brunch.</Description>
  </food>

  <food>
    <Name>Saag</Name>
    <Description>Leafy green curry made with spinach, mustard greens, or other seasonal greens.</Description>
  </food>

  <food>
    <Name>Keema</Name>
    <Description>Minced meat dish cooked with spices and often used as a filling for parathas or samosas.</Description>
  </food>

  <food>
    <Name>Chapli kebab</Name>
    <Description>Spiced minced meat patty made with ground beef or lamb.</Description>
  </food>
  
  <food>
    <Name>Tikka</Name>
    <Description>Marinated pieces of meat (chicken, beef, or lamb) grilled to perfection.</Description>
  </food>
  
  <food>
    <Name>Biryani</Name>
    <Description>Aromatic rice dish with meat (chicken, beef, or mutton), spices, and saffron.</Description>
  </food>

  <food>
    <Name>Halwa Puri</Name>
    <Description>Breakfast dish consisting of sweet semolina pudding (halwa) and deep-fried bread (puri).</Description>
  </food>

  <food>
    <Name>Chaat</Name>
    <Description>Street food snack with a mix of crispy fried dough, chickpeas, potatoes, yogurt, and tangy chutneys.</Description>
  </food>

  <food>
    <Name>Samosa</Name>
    <Description>Deep-fried pastry filled with spiced potatoes, peas, and sometimes meat.</Description>
  </food>
  
  <food>
    <Name>Pakora</Name>
    <Description>Batter-fried fritters made with vegetables (such as onions, potatoes, or spinach) or meat.</Description>
  </food>

  <food>
    <Name>Raita</Name>
    <Description>Cooling yogurt-based side dish with chopped vegetables (such as cucumbers, tomatoes, or onions) and spices.</Description>
  </food>

  <food>
    <Name>Jalebi</Name>
    <Description>Jalebi is a popular Pakistani sweet made by deep-frying a fermented batter in pretzel or circular shapes. 
    These crispy and syrupy treats are often enjoyed warm and are a favorite during festivals and special occasions.</Description>
  </food>

  <food>
    <Name>Kheer</Name>
    <Description>Kheer is a traditional rice pudding prepared by simmering rice, milk, sugar, and a variety of nuts and spices. 
    It is often garnished with almonds, pistachios, and rose petals, offering a creamy and indulgent dessert experience.</Description>
  </food>

  <food>
    <Name>Sheer Khurma</Name>
    <Description>Sheer Khurma is a special sweet dish prepared during the Islamic festival of Eid. 
    It is made by simmering vermicelli, milk, sugar, and a variety of nuts and dried fruits. 
    The dish is rich, creamy, and has a distinct flavor of rosewater and saffron.</Description>
  </food>

  <food>
    <Name>Gulab Jamun</Name>
    <Description>Gulab Jamun is a classic Pakistani dessert made of deep-fried dough balls soaked in a fragrant sugar syrup. 
    It is often flavored with rosewater, cardamom, and saffron, giving it a rich and aromatic taste.</Description>
  </food>

  <food>
    <Name>Barfi</Name>
    <Description>Barfi is a dense and fudge-like sweet made with condensed milk, sugar, and various flavors such as cardamom, pistachios, or coconut. 
    It is typically cut into square or diamond shapes and decorated with nuts.</Description>
  </food>

  <food>
    <Name>Falooda</Name>
    <Description>Falooda is a refreshing and indulgent dessert beverage consisting of a mix of vermicelli noodles, basil seeds, rose syrup, milk, and ice cream.
    It offers a unique combination of flavors and textures, making it a favorite summer treat.</Description>
  </food>

  <food>
    <Name>Ras Malai</Name>
    <Description>Ras Malai is a delectable dessert made from soft and creamy cheese dumplings soaked in sweetened milk flavored with cardamom and saffron. 
    It is often garnished with crushed pistachios and served chilled.</Description>
  </food>

  <food>
    <Name>Gajar ka Halwa</Name>
    <Description>Gajar ka Halwa, also known as carrot halwa, is a popular dessert made from grated carrots cooked in ghee (clarified butter), milk, sugar, and flavored with cardamom and nuts. 
    It has a rich, sweet, and slightly grainy texture.</Description>
  </food>


</FoodList>